Edwin Gonzalez

8023 glencannon dr Charlotte, NC, 28227 (917) 412-4456 edwin.gonzalez11@hotmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Quality-oriented professional with 4.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of conflict resolution, customer communications, and customer needs assessment. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Front end or Back end Web-Development role at your company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RGX Rims Charlotte, NC

Automotive Specialist

Dec 2014 – Present

- Examine vehicles, compile estimates of repair costs, and secure customers' approval to perform repairs.
- Enforce shop quality & safety guidelines.
- Inventory Management
- Train new technicians
- English to Spanish translator

Molina Installation Charlotte, NC

Lowes Installer Jan 2012 – Oct 2014

- Take measurements and study floor sketches to calculate the area to be carpeted and the amount of material needed.
- Draw building diagrams and record dimensions.
- Roll out, measure, mark, and cut carpeting to size with a carpet knife, following floor sketches and allowing extra carpet for final fitting.

Fernando's Auto-Body Charlotte, NC

Automotive Technician

Mar 2010 – Aug 2011

- Place wheels on balancing machines to determine counterweights required to balance wheels.
- Rotate tires to different positions on vehicles, using hand tools.
- Assist mechanics and perform other duties as directed.
- Drive automobile or service trucks to industrial sites to provide services or respond to emergency calls.
- Train new technicians
- English to Spanish translator

EDUCATION

UNC CHARLOTTE Charlotte, NC

Coding Bootcamp FullStack Web Development (Jul 2019)

• Relevant Coursework: Coding Bootcamp

NEW TECHNOLOGY AT GARINGER HIGH SCHOOL

Charlotte, NC

High School Diploma (Jun 2011)

• Extracurricular Activities: Fast Track TEN80 Racing Challenge, Fast Track TEN80 Computer Science Course

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Translator

CREDENTIALS AND LICENSES

UNC Charlotte Full Stack Web Development